<RECIPES>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Pineapple Upside Down Cake</TITLE>
            <BODY>Spray pan with non-stick cooking spray. Drain pineapple.
            Stir together melted margarine and brown sugar in 8-inch cake pan. Place pineapple slices in sugar mixture. Place cherry in center of each pineapple slice and in the center of the pan.
            Prepare cake mix according to the package directions. Pour cake batter evenly over pineapple.
            Bake at 350 degrees F, 25 to 30 minutes or until toothpick inserted in center comes out clean.
            Cool 5 minutes. Loosen edges and turn out onto serving platter.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Olive Oil Cranberry Bundt Cake</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Spray a 9 inch Bundt pan with cooking spray, and dust with flour.
            In a bowl, beat the egg whites until stiff. Beat in the sugar until fluffy. Mix in the olive oil.
            In a separate bowl, mix the flour, baking soda, salt, cinnamon, and cloves. Alternately mix the egg white mixture and the buttermilk into the flour mixture until smooth. Fold in the cranberries. Transfer the mixture to the prepared Bundt pan.
            Bake 1 hour in the preheated oven, until a knife inserted in the cake comes out clean.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        salad
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        breakfast
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Corn Tomato Salad</TITLE>
            <BODY>Place the corn in a large pot with enough water to cover, and bring to a boil. Cook 5 minutes, until kernels are tender but crisp. Drain, cool slightly, and use a knife to scrape kernels from the cobs.
            In a large bowl, mix the corn kernels, red bell pepper, onion, tomato, olive oil, balsamic vinegar, and garlic. Season with pepper. Chill 15 minutes before serving.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        breakfast
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Sara Jane's Oatmeal Cake</TITLE>
            <BODY>In a small bowl, stir oats into boiling water. Set aside to soak for 20 minutes.
			Preheat the oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Grease an 8x8 inch baking pan.
            In a medium bowl, cream together the white sugar, 1 cup brown sugar and shortening until smooth. Beat in the eggs one at a time. Sift in the flour, baking soda, salt and nutmeg; stir just until moistened. Mix in the soaked oats. Pour into the prepared pan, and spread evenly.
            Bake for 35 to 40 minutes in the preheated oven, until a toothpick inserted into the cake comes out clean. Turn the oven to the broil setting and let it heat up.
            In a small bowl, stir together the melted butter, 1/2 cup brown sugar, heavy cream, coconut and vanilla. Spread over the top of the cake. Broil for a few minutes, just until the coconut is lightly browned.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Chinese Garlic Chicken</TITLE>
            <BODY>Season chicken with salt and black pepper. Toss with flour until coated.
            Heat peanut oil in a wok or large skillet over high heat until it begins to smoke. Add chicken, and stir fry until the pieces are lightly browned on the outside, 3 to 5 minutes. Turn heat to medium and stir in whole garlic cloves; continue stir frying for 5 minutes.
            Turn heat to low, and add Shao-Hsing wine, soy sauce, and chicken stock. Cover, and simmer for 20 minutes until the chicken is tender. Remove garlic cloves before serving.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        pasta
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Chungles Pasta</TITLE>
            <BODY>In a large skillet heat the olive oil over medium high heat. Add the garlic and onion and saute until translucent.
            Add the tomato, olives, pepperoni, mushrooms, capers and salt and pepper to taste and simmer until heated through.
            Meanwhile, bring a large pot of lightly salted water to a boil. Add pasta and cook for 8 to 10 minutes or until al dente; drain.
            Add warm sauce to pasta and sprinkle with mozzarella cheese; mix well and serve immediately.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Uncle Terry Meat</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat an outdoor grill for medium heat and lightly oil grate.
            In a large, nonporous bowl, combine the oil, ketchup, wine, vinegar, garlic, salt, ground black pepper, mustard powder, celery salt and chili powder and mix well. Pierce the roast with a fork all over the meat. Place the meat in the bowl with the marinade and turn several times to coat. Cover and marinate in the refrigerator for at least 12 hours, turning occasionally.
            Grill over medium heat for 10 to 12 minutes per side, or until internal temperature reaches at least 145 degrees F (65 degrees C).</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        salad
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        breakfast
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Greek Salad IV</TITLE>
            <BODY>In a large bowl, combine the tomatoes, green bell pepper, cucumber, red onion, olive oil, and lemon juice. Refrigerate until thoroughly chilled. Sprinkle with feta cheese before serving.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        soup
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Italian Style Winter Soup</TITLE>
            <BODY>Heat oil in a large pot over medium heat. Add garlic and onion and saute for 3 minutes, or until tender. Add the sausage, browning well on all sides, about 5 minutes.
            Add the chicken stock, oregano, basil and parsley. Bring to a boil, reduce heat to low and simmer for 1 hour.
            Add the rice and simmer for 30 more minutes. Finally, add the cream, stirring well. Remove from heat and let soup rest for 5 minutes before serving.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        salad
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        breakfast
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Tuna Macaroni Salad</TITLE>
            <BODY>In a large pot of salted boiling water, cook pasta until al dente, rinse under cold water and drain.
            In a large bowl, combine pasta, tuna, peas and carrots.
            Whisk together the salad dressing mix, mayonnaise and milk. Stir into pasta mixture. Cover and refrigerate until chilled.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Hot and Spicy London Broil</TITLE>
            <BODY>Heat the oil in a large skillet over medium high heat. Place the meat in the oil and saute for 5 minutes per side.
            Pour out 1 cup of the pepper juice from the jar and pour into the skillet. Add the water, garlic salt and ground black pepper to taste.
            Reduce heat to low, cover and simmer for 40 minutes, flipping meat halfway through cooking. Add about 10 to 12 hot cherry peppers and heat for 5 more minutes.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Worm Cake</TITLE>
            <BODY>Prepare cake mix according to package directions. Pour batter into cupcake pans and bake as directed on cake mix box. Let cupcakes cool thoroughly before frosting.
            Spread cupcakes lightly with chocolate icing. Sprinkle cookie crumbs on top.
            Cut gummi worms in half (as many as you like). Put icing onto cut end of the worms and stick to the top of cupcakes. You can use as few or as many as will fit on each cupcake. Let icing set for 10 minutes and then enjoy.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Chicken Claridge Stew</TITLE>
            <BODY>Spray a large skillet with cooking spray. Saute the chicken in the oil. Add the onion and saute until translucent. Add the celery and carrots and saute briefly.
            Add the chicken soup, mushroom soup, water or broth, salt and pepper, sage and garlic. Do not add the tomatoes yet as they retard cooking time. Bring all to a boil, then cover and simmer for about 20 minutes. Add the tomatoes and simmer for 10 more minutes, uncovered. Serve over hot cooked rice if desired. Delicious!</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Botercake (Butter Cake)</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Grease and flour one 10 inch loaf pan.
            Mix grated lemon rind with 1 tablespoon sugar.
            Beat butter and sugar with vanilla sugar and lemon rind until the mixture becomes white and fluffy. Add eggs one at a time mixing after each one.
            Mix flour and baking powder together and then carefully fold into the butter and egg mixture. Pour batter into prepared loaf pan.
            Bake cake for 60 to 75 minutes or until a knife inserted in the middle comes out clean.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        salad
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        breakfast
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Cuban Grilled Chicken Salad</TITLE>
            <BODY>Toss the romaine with the onion, avocado, and peppers in a large bowl. Divide among four salad plates. Top each salad with a mound of black beans, some pineapple chunks, and the chopped chicken meat.
            Whisk together the olive oil with the garlic, salt, and pepper. Drizzle this dressing over each salad along with a little lime juice.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Wacky Cake III</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C).
            Sift the flour, white sugar, baking soda, salt and 6 tablespoons of the cocoa into a 9 x 13 inch baking pan.
            Drizzle melted margarine and the vinegar over the flour mixture. Add the vanilla and cold water and stir well to remove lumps.
            Bake at 350 degrees F (175 degrees C) for 35 minutes. Spread with chocolate frosting.
            To Make Chocolate Frosting: Combine the confectioner's sugar, 6 tablespoons water, 3 tablespoons cocoa, and 1/2 cup of the margarine. Heat until melted and stir until smooth add vanilla and nuts if desired, and spread over cake.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Italian Ricotta Cheesecake</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Coat two 9-inch pie pans with vegetable oil cooking spray.
            Beat eggs in a large bowl. Mix in the ricotta cheese, vanilla, cinnamon, sugar, zest, and whiskey. Pour into prepared pans.
            Bake in preheated oven for 1 hour to 1 hour 15 minutes, until firm. Let cool, then refrigerate until cold.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Black and Bleu Chicken Alfredo</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat an outdoor grill for high heat. Lightly oil grill grate. Season chicken on both sides with steak seasoning. Grill 6 to 8 minutes on each side, until juices run clear. Cool and slice.
            In a saucepan over low heat, mix the Alfredo sauce, bleu cheese dressing, and tomatoes. Cook and stir until the sauce boils.
            Bring a large pot of lightly salted water to a boil. Add angel hair pasta, cook 2 to 4 minutes, until al dente, and drain. Transfer to a large bowl, and toss with the grilled chicken and sauce to serve.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Sombrero Fajitas</TITLE>
            <BODY>Rub steaks with garlic powder and fajita seasoning, and cut into 1 1/2-inch strips. Set aside.
            In a large skillet over medium heat, cook bacon until just crisp and brown. Stir chopped onion, bell pepper, and cilantro into the skillet with the bacon. Add steak strips, and cook, stirring frequently, about 7 minutes. Stir in tomatoes, heat through; remove from heat, and top with Monterey Jack cheese.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Homemade Apple Crumble</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat oven to 375 degrees F (190 degrees C). Arrange apple pieces in baking dish, sprinkle with sugar, and cinnamon; toss well.
            In a bowl, combine the rice flour, almond meal, sugar, and coconut. Cut in butter until mixture is fine and crumbly. Sprinkle topping over apples
            Cover, and bake for 1 hour in the preheated oven, until the apples have lost their shape. Uncover, and continue to bake until crumble is crisp and golden in color.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        breakfast
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Fragrant and Healthy Carrot Cake</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat the oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Grease a 9 inch Bundt pan.
            In a large bowl, stir together the whole wheat flour, cake flour, brown sugar, cinnamon, carob, baking powder, baking soda and salt. Make a well in the center and pour in the molasses, oil, eggs and orange juice. Mix until the dry ingredients are moistened, then stir in the orange zest, lemon zest, raisins, figs, poppy seeds, carrots and pecans until evenly distributed. Pour into the prepared pan.
            Bake for 1 hour and 10 minutes in the preheated oven, or until a knife inserted into the center of the cake comes out clean. Cool for 30 minutes before removing from the pan.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Beef Stroganoff with White Wine</TITLE>
            <BODY>Melt the butter in a large saucepan over medium-high heat. Cook and stir the mushrooms, onion and garlic in the butter until tender. Reserving the liquid in the saucepan, remove the mushroom mixture to a bowl. Return the butter mixture to medium-high heat.
            Whisk together the flour and half-and-half until smooth; set aside.
            Season the beef with salt and pepper; cook the beef in the reserved liquid until browned, about 5 minutes. Stir the wine, beef bouillon, thyme, basil, oregano, bay leaves, and pepper; reduce heat to medium-low and simmer 10 minutes. Slowly stir in the flour mixture and simmer, stirring occasionally, until the sauce thickens, 20 to 30 minutes. Add the mushroom mixture and stir.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Ham and Green Bean Casserole</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Oil a 9-inch baking dish with spray cooking oil.
            Place the bread cubes in a small bowl. Melt the butter in a large skillet, and pour half over the bread cubes. Toss cubes and set the bowl aside.
            Add the onion to the remaining butter in the skillet and cook over medium heat until softened, about 2 minutes. Add the chopped ham. Stir in the cream of celery soup and the milk. Bring the mixture to a boil, stirring. Remove from heat.
            Put the rice and water into the baking dish. Top with the drained green beans. Then spoon the ham mixture on top of the green beans. Cover with the slices of American cheese, then sprinkle over all with the bread cubes.
            Bake uncovered until cheese melts and edges bubble, about 45 minutes.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Indian-Style Butter Chicken (Murgh Makhani)</TITLE>
            <BODY>Mix the ground red chile peppers, cinnamon, nutmeg, cloves, garam masala, salt, ginger, garlic, tomatoes, and yogurt in a large bowl. Stir the chicken pieces into the yogurt mixture, and let marinate in the refrigerator for 30 to 60 minutes.
            Melt the butter in a large skillet on medium heat and cook the bell pepper slices and onion until the onion begins to turn translucent, about 5 to 7 minutes, stirring occasionally. Add the chicken and marinade to the skillet. Cook, stirring constantly, 5 to 10 minutes until the chicken firms and is no longer pink in the center.
            Turn up heat to medium-high and mix in the cream and coriander. Cook until mixture just begins to boil, stirring continuously. Serve immediately.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        salad
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        breakfast
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Picnic Pasta Salad</TITLE>
            <BODY>Cook pasta in large pot of boiling salted water until al dente. Rinse with cool water. Drain well.
            Meanwhile, combine chopped vegetables, sugar, oil, mustard, mayonnaise, vinegar, and shredded Cheddar cheese in a large bowl. Season with salt and pepper to taste. Mix well. Stir in pasta. Refrigerate for 2 to 4 hours before serving.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        pasta
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        breakfast
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Microwave Macaroni and Cheese</TITLE>
            <BODY>In a large pot with boiling salted water cook the elbow macaroni until al dente. Drain and set aside.
            In a 2-quart microwave-safe covered casserole dish, cook the onions and butter or margarine on high for 3 to 4 minutes.
            Add the cooked and drained pasta, milk, and cubed cheese and stir. Cook for 11 to 12 minutes on high, stirring well after 4, 8, and 11 minutes. The mixture will still be runny at this stage. Add salt and pepper to taste.
            Let stand for 5-8 minutes before serving. The sauce will thicken as it cools slightly.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        soup
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Chunky Chicken Noodle Soup</TITLE>
            <BODY>Bring water, chicken stock, and chicken bouillon to a boil in a large stock pot. Add chicken breast, egg noodles, peas and carrots, chopped carrots, celery, onion, salt, black pepper, basil, bay leaf, and oregano. Continue to boil, uncovered, for 20 minutes. Reduce heat to medium and simmer until chicken is no longer pink in the center and noodles are tender, 5 to 10 minutes more.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Signature Pumpkin Pie</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat oven to 425 degrees F. Place pie crust on large foil-lined baking sheet.
            Mix pumpkin, milk, eggs and pumpkin pie spice in large bowl until smooth. Pour into crust.
            Bake 15 minutes. Reduce oven temperature to 350 degrees F. Bake 40 minutes longer or until knife inserted 1 inch from crust comes out clean. Cool completely on wire rack. Serve with Vanilla Whipped Cream, if desired.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Easy Slow Cooker Stroganoff</TITLE>
            <BODY>Mix cream of mushroom soup, mushrooms, butter, and onion in a slow cooker; add beef tips.
            Cook for 8 hours on Low.
            Bring a large pot of lightly salted water to a boil. Cook egg noodles in the boiling water, stirring occasionally until cooked through but firm to the bite, about 5 minutes. Drain.
            Serve beef tips and sauce over cooked egg noodles.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Gooseberry Pie I</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat oven to 400 degrees F (200 degrees C). Place a baking sheet on a lower oven rack.
            Stem and rinse berries.
            Crush 1/2 cup berries in the bottom of a saucepan. Combine sugar, tapioca, and salt; mix with crushed berries. Cook and stir until mixture boils. Cook for 2 more minutes. Remove from heat, and add in remaining whole berries.
            Pour fruit filling into pastry. Adjust top crust; cut slits to allow steam to escape. Brush top crust with milk and sugar.
            Bake in preheated oven on baking sheet until crust is golden brown and filling is bubbly, about 35 minutes.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Apple Cream Pie</TITLE>
            <BODY>Place apples in pie shell. Mix together sugar, flour, nutmeg, and cinnamon. Sprinkle this mixture over apples in shell.
            Melt the butter or margarine and stir into cream. Pour liquids over apples.
            Bake at 375 degrees F (190 degrees C) for 35 minutes.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>The Best Apple Pie Ever</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat an oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Stir together the sugar, cinnamon, and nutmeg in a small bowl; set aside. Press one of the pastries into the bottom of a 9-inch pie pan; reserve the crust.
            Toss the apples with maple syrup and vanilla extract. Spread 1/3 of the apples into the pie pan and sprinkle with the sugar mixture. Repeat the layers with the remaining apples and sugar. Cover the pie with the top crust and pinch the edges to seal.
            Bake in the preheated oven until the crust is golden brown, 30 to 35 minutes. Allow to cool before serving.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Sun Dried Tomato and Pine Nut Stuffed Beef Tenderloin</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat oven to 425 degrees F (220 degrees C).
            Heat 3 tablespoons olive oil in a skillet over a medium heat. Stir in pine nuts, and cook until golden brown. Remove with a slotted spoon, and drain on paper towels. Place shallots in the skillet. Cook and stir until tender, about 5 minutes. Mix in garlic and sun-dried tomatoes, and cook 2 minutes. Remove skillet from heat, mix in pine nuts, bread crumbs, and parsley. Season with salt and pepper, and set aside to cool.
            Slice the tenderloin lengthwise across the top about 2/3 of the way through the meat to create a pocket. Spread stuffing into the pocket. Wrap the tenderloin with kitchen twine to secure the stuffing, and transfer to a roasting pan. Rub the remaining olive oil over the surface of the meat. Season with salt and pepper.
            Roast in the preheated oven for 15 minutes. Lower oven temperature to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C) and continue cooking tenderloin 20 minutes, or to a minimum internal temperature of 145 degrees F (63 degrees C). Remove from oven and let the meat rest for 15 minutes before serving.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Robert Redford Cake</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C).
            In medium bowl, mix butter, flour, and chopped nuts. Press into 9x13 inch pan. Bake at 350 degrees F (175 degrees C) for 20 minutes. Cool completely.
            In a medium bowl, combine softened cream cheese and confectioners sugar, beat until smooth, then spread over cooled crust.
            In a large bowl, combine pudding mix with 3 cups milk. Beat until smooth, and spread over cream cheese layer.
            Spread whipped topping over pudding layer. Sprinkle with nuts. Refrigerate until ready to serve.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        salad
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        breakfast
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Christmas Red and Green Salad</TITLE>
            <BODY>Combine the corn, peas, beans, onions, celery and radish.
            Whisk together the salad dressing and milk or cream. Pour over salad, toss and refrigerate overnight.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Marsala Marinated Skirt Steak</TITLE>
            <BODY>Whisk Marsala wine, ketchup, garlic, kosher salt, rosemary, and black pepper together in a large glass or ceramic bowl. Add skirt steak and turn to evenly coat. Cover the bowl with plastic wrap, and marinate in the refrigerator, 8 hours to overnight.
            Preheat an outdoor grill for high heat, and lightly oil the grate.
            Remove steak from marinade, shake off excess, and discard marinade.
            Cook steak on the preheated grill until meat shines, 3 to 4 minutes per side. An instant-read thermometer inserted into the center should read 130 degrees F (54 degrees C). Transfer meat to a plate and let rest at least 5 minutes before slicing against the grain.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        soup
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Thai Chicken Vegetable Soup</TITLE>
            <BODY>Heat the oil in a 4-quart saucepan over medium-high heat. Add the carrot and pepper and cook for 5 minutes or until tender-crisp, stirring occasionally. Stir in the mushrooms, if desired.
            Add the broth to the saucepan and heat to a boil. Reduce the heat to medium-low. Stir in the chicken and cook for 5 minutes or until the chicken is hot, stirring occasionally.
            Stir in the coconut milk and cook until the mixture is hot and bubbling. Stir in the lime juice and cilantro just before serving.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>DanDan's Strawberry Cream Pie</TITLE>
            <BODY>Mix cream cheese, white sugar, and vanilla extract in a large bowl until smooth. Stir 3/4 cup mashed strawberries into cream cheese mixture.
            Beat heavy cream and confectioners' sugar in a glass or metal bowl until stiff peaks form. Lift your beater or whisk straight up: the cream will form sharp peaks. Fold whipped cream into cream cheese mixture until evenly mixed; fold in remaining 1/4 cup sliced strawberries.
            Spoon strawberry mixture into graham cracker crust. Chill at least 3 hours before serving.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        pasta
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Penne Pasta with Peas and Prosciutto</TITLE>
            <BODY>Heat oil in a large saucepan over medium-high heat. Saute onion and prosciutto in hot oil until onion is soft, 5 to 6 minutes. Stir garlic, salt, red pepper flakes, and black pepper into onion mixture; saute until fragrant, about 1 minute.
            Pour chicken broth, tomato sauce, and thyme into onion mixture. Add peas and beans; bring to a boil. Stir penne into broth mixture and cook for 7 minutes; remove from heat.
            Stir Parmesan cheese into penne mixture, cover the saucepan with a lid, and let sit until the pasta absorbs most of the liquid, about 5 minutes.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Shredded Barbeque Chicken</TITLE>
            <BODY>Put chicken breasts in a slow cooker and top with onion and barbeque sauce.
            Cook on High for 4 hours. Shred chicken with 2 forks and continue cooking Low for 4 hours more.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        soup
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Three Bean Soup</TITLE>
            <BODY>Heat a large pot over medium-high heat. Pour in oil and saute onion and garlic until golden-brown. Stir in tomatoes, kidney beans, garbanzo beans, lentils, tomato paste, oregano, pepper, and salt. Turn heat to low and simmer 20 minutes. Sprinkle in cheese and stir until melted. Serve immediately, or cool and freeze.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        salad
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        breakfast
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Seven Layer Mixed Up Salad</TITLE>
            <BODY>In a large bowl, gently mix the peas, sour cream, Cheddar cheese, green onions, celery, tomatoes, and bacon pieces. Season with salt, pepper, and dry ranch salad dressing mix. Chill at least 1 hour before serving.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        pasta
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Corny Spaghetti</TITLE>
            <BODY>Bring a large pot of lightly salted water to a boil. Add pasta and cook for 8 to 10 minutes or until al dente; drain.
            While pasta is cooking, in large skillet over medium heat, saute onion in butter 2 minutes. Stir in garlic and zucchini and cook 3 minutes more. Add mushrooms and cook 5 minutes more, until mushrooms are soft. Pour in red wine and pasta sauce, reduce heat to low and simmer. Add corn and bring back to a simmer again to heat through.
            Serve sauce over pasta with a dab of butter, or toss together.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        salad
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        breakfast
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Russian Cheese Salad</TITLE>
            <BODY>In a medium bowl, stir together the mozzarella cheese, mayonnaise and garlic. Chill until serving.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        salad
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        breakfast
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Waldorf Salad III</TITLE>
            <BODY>Dice apples with skin still on. Place in a bowl of water with a little lemon juice to keep them from turning brown.
            In a large bowl, whisk together the mayonnaise, sugar, lemon juice and orange juice. Fold in the whipped cream.
            Drain the apples and add to the mayonnaise mixture, along with the celery and raisins. Stir until ingredients are evenly coated.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Old Fashioned Fudge Cake</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Grease and flour a 9 inch tube pan. In small saucepan, heat butter, chocolate and water until chocolate melts and mixture is smooth, stirring constantly. Set aside to cool.
            Sift together into a large bowl the flour, sugar and baking soda. In a small bowl, beat egg slightly and combine with sour cream and vanilla. Stir into flour mixture. Pour in the cooled chocolate mixture. Beat at low speed for 5 minutes until completely combined and the consistency of heavy cream.
            Pour batter into prepared 9 inch tube pan. Bake in the preheated oven for 45 to 60 minutes, or until a toothpick inserted into the center of the cake comes out clean. Let cool in pan for 10 minutes, then turn out onto a wire rack and cool completely.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        soup
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Potato (Velveeta\u00ae) Cheese Soup</TITLE>
            <BODY>Combine the water, potatoes, processed cheese, onion, bouillon, parsley, salt, pepper, and Cajun seasoning in a large pot. Bring to a boil over high heat. Reduce heat to medium-low; cover and simmer until the potatoes are tender, about 30 minutes.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Flat Iron Steaks Marinated in Red Wine</TITLE>
            <BODY>Whisk together 2 tablespoons of olive oil, 3 cloves minced garlic, parsley, thyme, red wine, 1/2 teaspoon mustard powder, salt, and pepper until combined. Pour into a resealable plastic bag over the flat iron steaks. Squeeze out excess air, seal, and marinate for 1 hour at room temperature, or 4 hours in the refrigerator.
            Preheat an outdoor grill for medium-high heat and lightly oil grate. Stir together 2 cloves minced garlic, 1/2 teaspoon mustard powder, and 1/2 teaspoon olive oil in a small bowl and set aside.
            Remove steaks from the marinade, shake off excess, and discard remaining marinade. Cook on preheated grill to desired degree of doneness, about 4 minutes per side for medium-rare. Brush with reserved garlic mixture before serving.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Yazdi Cakes</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat the oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Sift the flour and baking powder into a bowl; set aside. Grease the cups of a cupcake/muffin pan. You will need 24 cups.
            Combine the eggs and sugar in a large heatproof bowl and set on top of a pan of simmering water. Beat constantly with a whisk or electric mixer until thick and pale, about 8 minutes. Remove from the heat and continue to beat until cooled, about 10 minutes. Mix in the butter, yogurt, cardamom and rose water. Stir in the flour mixture by hand and fold in the slivered almonds. Spoon into the prepared cupcake molds, filling 3/4 full. Sprinkle some chopped pistachios over the tops.
            Bake in the preheated oven until firm to the touch and golden brown, 25 to 30 minutes.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        soup
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Best Beer Cheese Soup</TITLE>
            <BODY>Place bacon in a large, deep skillet. Cook over medium-high heat until evenly brown; drain on plate lined with paper towels; crumble.
            Melt the butter in a skillet over medium heat. Cook the onion, carrot, and celery in the butter until soft, 7 to 10 minutes. Add the bacon, basil, oregano, and green onions; cook and stir 2 minutes. Stir the flour into the mixture until completely dissolved. Pour in the chicken broth and beer; cook until heated through. Melt the processed cheese food and Cheddar cheese in the mixture in small batches. Season with garlic powder and stir.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Granny's Beef Stew</TITLE>
            <BODY>Heat oil in a large pot over medium heat. Coat beef with flour. Place in the pot, and evenly brown on all sides.
            Place 2 cups boiling water, Worcestershire sauce, and garlic powder into pot with beef. Season with salt and pepper. Reduce heat to low, and simmer beef for 2 hours, or until tender.
            Add onion, carrots, diced tomatoes and potatoes to pot. Continue cooking 30 minutes to 1 hour, until vegetables are soft.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        soup
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Hearty Chicken Vegetable Soup I</TITLE>
            <BODY>Place chicken, onion, celery, salt, basil, and pepper in a 10 quart stock pot. Fill stock pot with water until ingredients are fully covered and bring to a boil. Let simmer for 1 and 1/2 hours or until chicken is tender.
            Remove chicken from pot with slotted spoon and set aside for later.
            Add carrots, squash, zucchini, mushrooms, red pepper, tortellini, chicken soup base and uncooked noodles to stock pot and increase temperature to medium heat.
            While noodles and vegetables are cooking, tear chicken apart from bones. Cut up into pieces and add to soup in stock pot. Be sure to add additional water if ingredients are not fully covered. Bring to a boil, then reduce to a simmer for about 10 minutes or just until noodles are cooked. Enjoy</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        soup
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Oriental Hot 'n' Sour Soup</TITLE>
            <BODY>In a large cooking pot, add chicken broth, ginger root, and peppercorns, and bring to boil. Reduce heat to low and simmer uncovered for 20 minutes.
            Strain broth, discard ginger root and peppercorns. Return strained broth to pot. Add green onions, red pepper, mushrooms, bamboo shoots, rice wine vinegar, chili powder, and sesame oil. Simmer for 10 minutes or until vegetables are just tender. Serve in soup bowls over cooked white or brown rice.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        soup
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Creamy Pea Soup</TITLE>
            <BODY>Place split peas, water, ham bone, shallots, carrots, celery leaves, bay leaf, salt, garlic and pepper into a large pot. Heat to almost boiling. Reduce heat, cover, and simmer for about 1 1/2 hours or until the peas are tender. Remove the ham bone and the bay leaf. Dice the meat from the ham bone and set aside.
            Cut the cream cheese into cubes. Process cream cheese with the soup in small batches in a blender or food processor.
            Add ham, and reheat. Taste, and adjust seasonings as necessary.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Old-Fashioned Honey Pecan Pie</TITLE>
            <BODY>In a saucepan bring the honey to a boil. Quickly beat the eggs into the honey. Add butter, vanilla, nuts, and nutmeg. Pour into the pie shell.
            Bake at 325 degrees F (165 degrees C) for 25 minutes or until set.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        soup
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Senate Bean Soup</TITLE>
            <BODY>Put beans in a large bowl, add water to cover and soak overnight. In a large saucepan over medium heat, combine the ham shank and 4 cups water and simmer for about 45 minutes. When cool enough to handle, remove meat from bone and shred meat. Set bone and meat aside for later. (Note: reserve the stock, if desired, to replace the ham base.)
            Drain the beans. In an 8 quart pot over high heat, combine the beans, 12 cups fresh water and ham base. (Note: At this point, if desired, measure reserved stock from step 1, add water to total 12 cups liquid, and use this mixture to eliminate the ham base.) Add the onion, carrot, celery, garlic powder, ham, ham bone and salt and pepper to taste.
            Bring the mixture to a boil, reduce heat to medium, cover and simmer for 1 1/2 hours, or until beans are tender. Add additional water as needed. (Note: Soup should be thick enough to heavily coat a spoon.)</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Chicken with Mustard Sauce</TITLE>
            <BODY>In a large, resealable plastic bag, mix flour, salt, and pepper. Place cubed chicken in the bag, and shake to coat.
            Melt butter in a medium skillet over medium heat, and saute the chicken until browned. Remove chicken from the skillet and set aside.
            Stir shallot into the skillet, and saute until tender. Mix in vermouth, chicken broth, Dijon mustard, and stone ground mustard.
            Return chicken to the skillet, and blend in the heavy cream. Cover, reduce heat, and simmer about 15 minutes, until the vermouth mixture has thickened. Mix in parsley, lemon juice, and lemon pulp just before serving.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Ginger Beef</TITLE>
            <BODY>In a large bowl, mix onions, garlic, ginger, turmeric, dried chile pepper, and salt. Place flank steak in the mixture, and toss to coat. Cover, and place in the refrigerator at least 15 minutes.
            Heat oil in a Dutch oven over medium high heat, and stir in onion and steak mixture. Cook and stir until steak is lightly browned. Mix in tomatoes, and cook over high heat about 10 minutes.
            Mix onion soup into the Dutch oven. Cover, reduce heat, and simmer 1 hour, until meat is tender.
            Place rice and water in a medium saucepan, and bring to a boil. Cover, reduce heat, and simmer 20 minutes. Serve the steak mixture over the cooked rice.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        soup
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Spanish Garlic and Vegetable Soup</TITLE>
            <BODY>Heat oil in a large pot over medium heat. Add carrot, cabbage, cauliflower and leeks. Cook, stirring constantly, for a few minutes until cabbage wilts. Stir in the garlic and tomato paste, and continue to cook for another minute or two, stirring constantly to prevent the garlic from burning. Stir in 2 cups of water, then cover and simmer for 10 minutes.
            Pour in the diced tomatoes and the remaining 2 cups of water, and return to a boil. Reduce heat to low, cover and simmer for 20 minutes.
            Reserve 2 cups of the liquid, and puree the remaining soup in a blender or food processor. Return the blended mixture to the reserved liquid, and stir in milk and butter. Return to a boil, and cook for 1 minute. Season to taste with salt and pepper, and serve.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        soup
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Tomato Garbanzo Soup with Rice</TITLE>
            <BODY>Place the diced tomatoes with juice and water in a large pot, and bring to a boil. Mix in the rice and carrots, and season with cumin, chili powder, red pepper, salt, and black pepper. Reduce heat to low, cover, and simmer 25 minutes, or until rice and carrots are tender.
            Mix the garbanzo beans into the pot, and continue cooking 5 minutes, until heated through.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        soup
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Carrot and Cilantro Soup</TITLE>
            <BODY>Heat the olive oil in a large pot over medium heat, and cook the onions, carrots, garlic, and chile pepper until tender. Mix in tomatoes, vegetable stock, 1/2 the cilantro, balsamic vinegar, sugar, brown sauce, and Worcestershire sauce. Season with salt and pepper. Bring to a boil. Reduce heat to low, and simmer 30 minutes.
            Transfer the soup in batches to a blender or food processor, and blend until smooth. Return to the pot, and continue cooking until heated through.
            Remove soup from heat, and mix in the cream. Finely chop the remaining cilantro, and mix into the soup to serve.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        salad
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        breakfast
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Thai Salad with Whole Grain Brown Rice and Chicken</TITLE>
            <BODY>Cook the rice according to package directions, set aside and chill.
            Whisk the peanut butter, vinegar, oil, soy sauce, sugar, ginger, garlic, and poblano peppers in a small bowl, set aside.
            Cut the cucumbers in half lengthwise before cutting them into 1/2-inch slices.
            Combine the rice with cucumber, dressing, chicken, and onion. Cover and chill.
            Just before serving, toss the salad with the spinach and basil.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Chicken with a Creamy Marsala Sauce</TITLE>
            <BODY>Mix flour, salt, and pepper in a shallow dish. Press chicken tenders in the flour to coat completely; shake gently to remove any excess flour.
            Heat olive oil in a large skillet over medium, tilting the pan to coat the cooking surface in oil. Melt the butter in the skillet. Cook the chicken tenders in the hot butter until evenly browned, 7 to 8 minutes.
            Pour the Marsala wine into the skillet and bring to a boil while scraping the browned bits of food off of the bottom of the pan with a wooden spoon; cook until the wine is hot, about 30 seconds. Pour chicken stock into the skillet.
            Stir heavy cream and mustard together in a bowl; add to the skillet. Bring the mixture to a simmer and cook another 10 minutes.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Swanny's Killer Fajitas</TITLE>
            <BODY>Place chicken strips in a bowl and stir in lime juice, cumin, paprika, chili powder, cayenne pepper, and black pepper; marinate chicken for 15 to 30 minutes.
            Heat a large skillet or wok over medium heat and pour in olive oil. Cook and stir red bell pepper and onion in the hot oil until softened, about 5 minutes; move vegetables to the outer edge of the skillet.
            Place chicken strips with marinade in the center of the skillet and cook and stir until chicken is no longer pink in the center and juices run clear, about 3 minutes; cook and stir chicken and vegetables together until liquid in skillet has evaporated, about 2 more minutes. Set chicken and vegetables aside.
            Place corn tortillas on a microwave-safe plate with damp paper towels separating each tortilla. Cook in microwave until tortillas are hot and flexible, about 30 seconds.
            Place corn tortillas onto 4 serving plates; spread each tortilla with 1 tablespoon sour cream.
            Top each tortilla with 1/4 of the chicken and vegetable mixture; sprinkle with 2 tablespoons shredded Cheddar-Monterey Jack cheese blend.
            Sprinkle each tortilla with 1/4 cup lettuce and 2 tablespoons diced tomato.
            Top with any other desired toppings; repeat with remaining tortillas and ingredients.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        pasta
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Bolognese with Homemade Noodles</TITLE>
            <BODY>Mix the bread flour and flax seed meal together on a clean surface or in a bowl. Make a well in the center for the flour mixture, then crack the eggs into the center. Mix the eggs with your fingers. Gradually incorporate the flour from the sides of the well until dough is firm. Knead dough until smooth, about 5 minutes. Remove excess flour, allow the dough to rest for 1 minute.
            Roll out the dough with a pasta machine or with a rolling pin until very thin. Sprinkle the sheets with a little flour, roll up each sheet of pasta, then slice them into strips. Toss with flour and set aside until ready to cook.
            Heat a large skillet over high heat. Stir in the beef, onion, garlic, and carrots. Cook and stir until the beef is crumbly, evenly browned, and no longer pink. Drain and discard any excess grease. Stir in the oregano, garlic powder, bay leaf, salt, and black pepper. Add the tomatoes and water. Bring to boil, then reduce heat to medium-low and continue to simmer for 1 to 1 1/2 hours. Pour all but 2 cups of the sauce in an airtight container and freeze for future use.
            Fill a large pot with lightly salted water and bring to a rolling boil over high heat. Once the water is boiling, stir in the noodles, and return to a boil. Cook until the pasta floats to the top, 4 to 5 minutes; drain.
            Stir butter and Parmesan cheese into reserved 2 cups of sauce over medium heat. Stir noodles into sauce, and toss until pasta is well-coated. Serve in large bowls with more Parmesan cheese.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        pasta
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Salad Stuffed Shells</TITLE>
            <BODY>Bring a large pot of lightly salted water to a boil. Cook pasta shells in the boiling water, stirring occasionally until cooked through but firm to the bite, about 8 minutes. Drain and rinse with cold water until chilled.
            Combine salami, romaine lettuce, roma tomatoes, cucumber, and red onion in a large bowl; pour balsamic vinaigrette dressing over salad and toss to coat. Stuff pasta shells with lettuce mixture and sprinkle with Parmesan cheese.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        soup
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Lentil Tomato Soup</TITLE>
            <BODY>Melt the butter in a large pot over medium high heat. Place the onions in the pot and saute for 10 minutes, or until onions are tender.
            Place the tomatoes in a food processor or blender and puree until smooth. Pour this into the pot with the onion along with the chicken broth and the lentils
            Bring to a boil, reduce heat to low and let simmer for 20 minutes. Then, stir in the wine, garlic, nutmeg and cloves. Simmer for at least 25 more minutes.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Kamikaze Burgers</TITLE>
            <BODY>In a large bowl, mix ground beef, onion and garlic. Season with salt and pepper, and shape into 4 patties.
            Preheat an outdoor grill for medium heat, and lightly oil grate.
            Place patties on the prepared grill, and cook 5 minutes per side, or to desired doneness.
            Prepare buns by spreading 1 tablespoon of wasabi on the bottom half, and 1 tablespoon mayonnaise on the top half. Top burgers with a slice of cheese, and sandwich inside the buns.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Steve's Bodacious Barbecue Ribs</TITLE>
            <BODY>In a medium bowl, stir together paprika, cayenne pepper, garlic powder, onion powder, salt, ground black pepper, cumin, brown sugar, cinnamon, cloves, and nutmeg. Apply liberally to the ribs. Place ribs in a large roasting pan, cover, and refrigerate overnight. Remove ribs from the refrigerator 1 hour before smoking.
            Prepare an outdoor smoker, bringing the temperature to 200 to 225 degrees F (95 to 110 degrees C).
            Smoke ribs for 6 to 8 hours, adding wood chips to maintain a steady smoke (approximately one handful every 30 to 45 minutes). Ribs are done when crispy outside and tender inside. Remove from smoker, and set aside for 15 to 20 minutes before serving.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Moist Chocolate Cake</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Grease and flour a 9x13 or two 9 inch round pans. Sift together the flour, baking powder, baking soda and salt. Set aside. In a small bowl, combine hot coffee with 1 cup cocoa and let cool to lukewarm.
            In a large bowl, cream together the 1/2 cup butter and 1 cup sugar until light and fluffy. Add the eggs one at a time, beating well with each addition, then stir in the 1 teaspoon vanilla. Add the flour mixture alternately with the coffee and cocoa mixture; beat well.
            Pour batter into a 9x13 inch cake or two 9 inch round pans. Bake in the preheated oven for 45 minutes or until a toothpick inserted into the cake comes out clean. Allow to cool.
            To make the frosting: In a medium bowl, combine confectioners sugar, 1 cup cocoa, 1/2 cup butter and 1 1/4 teaspoons vanilla. Mix until smooth. Add hot milk a teaspoon at a time to make a smooth, spreadable consistency. Spread onto cooled cake.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        soup
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Restaurant-Style Cheesy Poblano Pepper Soup</TITLE>
            <BODY>Cut the corn tortillas into ninths, place into a food processor and chop until fine. Add the flour, chili powder, cumin, salt and pepper. Blend until tortillas become the consistency of cornmeal. Set aside.
            In a large pot over medium heat, combine the oil, onion, 1/2 cup poblano chile peppers and garlic and saute for 5 minutes, or until onions are translucent. Add the butter or margarine and allow it to melt. Add the ground tortilla mixture to the pot and stir well with a wire whip to form a roux. (Note: Do not let it burn.)
            While stirring, slowly add the chicken stock. Make sure to scrape the sides and bottom of the pot. Add the half-and-half, bring to a slow simmer and cook for 7 to 10 minutes. (Note: Do not let soup come to a hard boil.)
            Turn off heat and allow soup to cool slightly. Stir in the chicken before serving. Top each serving with the cheese, poblano chile peppers and tortilla strips for garnish.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        soup
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Chili Soup</TITLE>
            <BODY>In a large pot over medium heat, combine the ground beef and onions. Saute for 5 minutes, or until meat is browned. Drain excess fat and add the potatoes, beans, tomato soup, tomato juice, chili powder, water and salt to taste. Bring just to a boil and reduce heat to low. Simmer for 1 hour and serve.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        salad
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        breakfast
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Creamy Fruit Salad II</TITLE>
            <BODY>Combine the cream cheese and condensed milk; blend until smooth.
            Drain the juice from 1 can of the fruit cocktail and add to cream cheese mixture. Add the other can with all its juice and any other fruit at this time. Mix with a large spoon.
            Add extra condensed milk to sweeten if desired. Cover with saran wrap and chill. Mix well and serve cold..</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Cheesecake</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat oven to 325 degrees F (165 degrees C). In a large bowl, combine cream cheese, 1 cup sugar, almond extract, eggs and salt. Beat until smooth. Pour into a greased deep dish pie plate.
            Bake at 325 degrees F (165 degrees C) for 45 to 50 minutes. Remove from oven and let cool for 20 minutes.
            To Make Topping: combine sour cream, 2 tablespoons sugar and 1/4 teaspoon vanilla extract and stir until smooth. Spread evenly on top of the baked cheesecake, then bake 10 minutes at 325 degrees F (165 degrees C) to set the top.
            Let cool, refrigerate several hours before serving.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Sticky Chicken</TITLE>
            <BODY>Place chicken pieces in a shallow casserole dish.
            Mix together oil, ketchup, chutney, garlic, salt, black pepper, pepper sauce, and lemon juice. Pour over chicken pieces.
            Bake at 400 degrees F (205 degrees C) for 20 minutes. Reduce heat to 325 degrees F (165 degrees C). Bake a further 30 minutes, or until pieces are tender and cooked through.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Amazing Corn Cake</TITLE>
            <BODY>Stir together flour, baking powder, baking soda, cinnamon, and salt.
            In a mixing bowl, combine corn and sugars. Beat in eggs and oil till well blended. Mix flour mixture into batter. Stir in raisins and nuts. Pour batter into greased 9 x 13 inch pan.
            Bake at 350 degrees F (175 degrees C) for 30 to 35 minutes, or till cake tests done. Cool.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Orange Chiffon Cake</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat oven to 325 degrees F (165 degrees C). Wash angel food tube pan in hot soapy water to ensure it is totally grease free.
            Sift flour, sugar, baking powder, and salt together into bowl. Make a well in center. Put egg yolks, cooking oil, orange juice, orange rind, and vanilla into well. Set aside. Don't beat yet.
            In a large bowl, beat egg whites and cream of tartar in mixing bowl until very stiff. Set aside.
            Using same beaters, beat egg yolk-flour mixture until smooth. Gently fold 1/4 at a time into egg whites. Pour batter into ungreased 10 inch angel food tube pan.
            Bake in oven for 60 to 70 minutes, until an inserted wooden pick comes out clean. Invert pan until cake has cooled. Remove from pan. Serve plain or frost with Orange Icing.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Strawberry Angels' Cake</TITLE>
            <BODY>Bake cake for filling according to package directions. Let cool.
            Slice angel food cake in half horizontally. Creat a tunnel for the filling by removing a small amount of the interior of the bottom half of the cake.
            In a bowl combine cream, confectioners' sugar and cocoa; whip until soft peaks form. Fold half the strawberries into half the whipped cream; spoon into cake tunnel, pressing down firmly.
            Replace top of cake; pressing gently. Frost cake with remaining cream mixture. Cover top of cake with remaining strawberries. Chill about 15 minutes before slicing. Serves 10-12 people.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Fruit Filled Cheesecake</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C).
            In a medium bowl, combine flour, oats, baking powder, brown sugar and butter. Press all but 3/4 cup of the crumb mixture into the bottom of a 10 inch round baking pan. Spread the fruit pie filling over the top and sprinkle with the remaining crumbs. Bake at 350 degrees F (175 degrees C) for 15 minutes. Remove from oven and let cool for 10 minutes.
            In a large bowl, beat the cream cheese and sugar together. Add the vanilla and sour cream and beat until smooth. Beat in the eggs one at a time. Pour batter into the prepared crust. Place the pan in a large roasting pan and place in the oven. Fill the roasting pan with water to the 1 inch mark. Bake at 350 degrees F (175 degrees C) for 55 minutes. Remove cake from oven, cool to room temperature and refrigerate overnight.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Herman Coffee Cake</TITLE>
            <BODY>Bring Herman Starter to room temperature.
			Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Grease and lightly flour one 9x13 inch baking pan.
            Stir together Herman Starter, oil and beaten eggs.
			Stir together the flour, cinnamon, baking soda, baking powder, salt and white sugar. Stir in nuts and raisins. Add the flour mixture to the egg mixture and stir well. Pour into the prepared pan and sprinkle with the topping.
            To Make Topping: Combine the 1 cup brown sugar, 3 tablespoons flour, 1 teaspoon cinnamon. Cut in 1/4 cup softened butter, until the mixture resembles very coarse crumbs.
            Bake in a preheated 350 degrees F (175 degrees C) for 30 to 40 minutes. While still hot pour glaze over the top and serve.
            To Make Glaze: In a small saucepan, melt 1/2 cup butter or margarine. Stir in the milk and 1 cup brown sugar. Bring to a boil and let boil for 3 minutes. Immediately pour over hot cake.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Zucchini Chocolate Rum Cake</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Grease and flour a 10 inch Bundt pan.
            In a large bowl, cream butter and sugar until light and fluffy. Add eggs one at a time, beating well with each addition. Stir in Zucchini and 1/3 cup rum.
            In a separate bowl, mix flour with nuts, chocolate, cocoa, baking powder, soda, salt and cinnamon. Stir flour mixture and milk into egg mixture until well blended.
            Spread Batter into 10 inch Bundt pan. Bake at 350 degrees F (175 degrees C) for 50 to 55 minutes, or until toothpick inserted into center of cake comes out clean. Let cake cool in pan for 15 minutes, then invert onto wire rack and cool completely. Drizzle with rum glaze.
            Rum Glaze: In a medium bowl, combine confectioners sugar with 3 tablespoons rum. Mix until smooth.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Jamaican Style Curry Chicken</TITLE>
            <BODY>Heat vegetable oil in a skillet over medium-high heat; cook and stir onion, tomato, garlic, curry powder, habanero pepper, and thyme until onion is golden, about 7 minutes. Stir in chicken and cook until chicken is lightly browned, about 5 minutes.
            Pour water into the skillet, reduce heat to low; cover and simmer until chicken is no longer pink at the center, about 30 minutes. Season with salt.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        soup
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Vegetable Tom Yum Soup</TITLE>
            <BODY>Bring chicken stock, galangal, lime leaves, lemon grass, and hot chile paste to a boil in a large pot. Stir in fish sauce, lime juice, shallots, tomato, mushrooms, bok choy, and carrot. Reduce heat to medium-low, and simmer until the vegetables are tender, about 25 minutes. Garnish with cilantro and green onion before serving.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        soup
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Turkey Soup with Root Vegetables</TITLE>
            <BODY>Bring the turkey carcass and water to a boil in a large pot over high heat. Skim off and discard any scum that forms. Add the chopped celery, chopped carrots, chopped Spanish onion, 1/4 bunch parsley, bay leaves, and peppercorns and return to a simmer. Reduce heat to medium-low and simmer uncovered for 3 hours. Strain the turkey broth through a mesh sieve and skim off any fat that floats to the surface.
            Heat the olive oil in a large pot over medium heat. Stir in the red onion; cook until the onion has softened and turned translucent, about 5 minutes. Add the diced celery, diced carrots, parsnip, and rutabaga; cook 5 minutes more. Stir in the garlic and chopped parsley, and cook for 1 minute more. Pour in the turkey broth, season to taste with salt and pepper, and bring to a simmer over high heat.
            Reduce heat to medium-low and simmer until the vegetables are nearly tender, 15 to 20 minutes. Stir in the orzo and cook until just tender, about 7 minutes. Cover and remove the pot from the heat. Let stand until the orzo is tender, about 5 minutes.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        soup
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Cream of Potato Soup III</TITLE>
            <BODY>In a large pot over high heat, boil the potatoes in the broth for 15 minutes, or until potatoes are tender. Carefully separate the potatoes from the broth and transfer to a blender or food processor.
            Add 3/4 cup of the broth to the potatoes and puree for 5 seconds or more depending on how smooth you want the soup to be. Add remaining broth and set aside.
            Melt the butter in a large saucepan over medium heat. Add the salt, ground black pepper, onion and dill weed to the butter, stir and saute for 2 minutes. Sprinkle with the flour and stir well.
            Pour in the milk and heat until the mixture starts to thicken, about 1 to 2 minutes. Stir in the pureed potato mixture. Allow to heat through and serve.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Hornets Nest Cake</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Grease and flour a 9x13 inch pan.
            Prepare pudding as directed on box. Allow to cool slightly. Mix in yellow cake mix. Stir well. Pour batter into 9x13 cake pan. Sprinkle top with butterscotch chips and chopped walnuts.
            Bake in preheated oven for 35 to 40 minutes. Cut into squares and serve.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Tangerine Orange Cake</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat oven to 325 degrees F (165 degrees C). Grease a 10 inch Bundt pan or line a muffin pan with paper cups.
            In a medium bowl, stir together the cake mix and instant pudding. Add the tangerine juice, oil, eggs and lemon extract, mix until well blended. Pour into the prepared pan or pans.
            Bake for 35 to 40 minutes in the preheated oven, until the cake springs back to the touch. For cupcakes, bake for 15 to 17 minutes. Let cool in the pan for 10 minutes before removing from pan to cool completely.
            In a small saucepan, combine the remaining tangerine juice, sugar and butter over medium heat. Stir frequently until the mixture is smooth. Drizzle over cooled cake or cupcakes.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        pasta
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Vegetarian Lentil Spaghetti</TITLE>
            <BODY>Place the lentils, tomatoes and artichokes (with the liquid from the cans), 1/8 teaspoon cayenne pepper and the water into a large saucepan. Bring to a boil. Reduce heat to low and simmer until lentils are tender, about 20 minutes.
            Meanwhile, bring a large pot of lightly salted water and 1 tablespoon of the olive oil to a boil. Add spaghetti and cook for 8 to 10 minutes or until al dente; drain. Return pasta to pot and cover to keep warm.
            Heat remaining 2 tablespoons olive oil in a small skillet over medium heat and cook green onions for about 3 minutes. Add 1/8 teaspoon cayenne pepper and sesame seeds and cook until the seeds are lightly browned, about 2 minutes. Set aside.
            Add the lentil mixture to the pot of pasta and toss to distribute evenly. Add the green onion mixture and toss lightly again. Season with salt and pepper to taste.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        salad
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        breakfast
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Speedy Pear and Pecan Salad</TITLE>
            <BODY>Place the salad greens, pear pieces, pecans, and mozzarella cheese in a bowl. Pour the Italian dressing over the salad mixture, and toss to coat evenly.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        salad
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        breakfast
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Barbeque Potato Salad</TITLE>
            <BODY>Place cubed potatoes into a large kettle and cover with water. Bring to a boil over medium-high heat, then reduce heat to medium-low, cover, and simmer until the potatoes are just tender, 15 to 20 minutes. Drain and spread the potatoes onto baking sheets in a single layer. Chill the potatoes in the refrigerator until cold, about 2 hours.
            Mix the cooled potatoes, red onion, egg, mayonnaise, barbeque sauce, garlic powder, salt, and pepper in a large bowl. Sprinkle with paprika if desired.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        salad
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        breakfast
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Carrot Salad</TITLE>
            <BODY>In a large bowl, toss together the carrots, pineapple, marshmallows, raisins and celery.
            Whisk together the salad dressing and sugar; pour over salad and toss. Chill for at least 12 hours.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        pasta
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Vegetable Pasta Casserole</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C).
            Bring a large pot of lightly salted water to a boil. Add pasta and cook for 8 to 10 minutes. Stir in broccoli, mushrooms and green pepper, and cook 6 to 8 minutes more, or until pasta is al dente; drain.
            Meanwhile, melt butter in a medium saucepan over medium-high heat. Saute onions and garlic for 1 to 2 minutes. Stir in flour and milk; cook 5 minutes, or until mixture coats the back of a spoon. Remove from heat and stir in 1/2 cup Parmesan cheese, salt and pepper.
            In a 9x13 inch baking dish combine pasta, vegetables, milk mixture and 4 tablespoons basil. Sprinkle with bread crumbs, 2 tablespoons Parmesan cheese, and remaining 1 tablespoon basil. Coat with butter flavored cooking spray.
            Bake in preheated oven for 30 minutes, or until golden brown.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        pasta
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Cheesy Turkey with Pasta</TITLE>
            <BODY>Bring a large pot of lightly salted water to a boil. Add pasta and cook for 8 to 10 minutes or until al dente; drain.
            In a large saucepan or deep skillet, melt the butter over low to medium heat; blend in flour. Slowly add turkey stock, pasta sauce, and water. Mix well. Stir in onion soup mix and garlic; season with salt and pepper.
            Sprinkle in the Monterey Jack, Cheddar cheese and turkey. Stir until the cheese is melted and the meat is heated through. Spoon sauce over pasta and serve.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Joey's Cheesecake</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat oven to 375 degrees F (190 degrees C.)
            In a large bowl, beat the cream cheese, sugar and vanilla until smooth. Beat in eggs, one at a time. Stir in yogurt. Pour filling into crust.
            Bake in the preheated oven for 30 to 40 minutes, or until filling is set. Refrigerate at least 4 hours before serving.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Hot Lips Chicken</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C).
            Spread the crushed chips in the bottom of a 9x13 inch baking dish to form crust. Layer shredded chicken on top. In a small bowl mix together the yellow bell pepper, red bell pepper, onion and tomatoes and spread this mixture on top of chicken. In a separate bowl mix together the cream of mushroom soup, cream of chicken soup, enchilada sauce and water. Pour this mixture over all and top with cheese.
            Bake in the preheated oven for 25 minutes, or until cheese is brown and bubbly.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Ground Beef and Sausage in Red Beans and Rice</TITLE>
            <BODY>Prepare the rice in a large pot according to package directions.
			Cut the kielbasa into 1-inch chunks and quarter the chunks. Place in a large skillet over medium-high heat for about 5 to 10 minutes, or until lightly browned. Season with cayenne pepper to taste. Transfer this to the pot with the rice, reserving the grease in the skillet.
            In the same skillet over medium-high heat, saute the ground beef for 5 minutes. Stir in the rice, and onion; reduce heat to medium and saute for 5 more minutes. Drain well and add to the pot. Stir the kidney beans, pinto beans, and pork and beans into the pot. Add a little water, if necessary, and simmer over low heat until ready to serve.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        salad
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        breakfast
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Ribbon Salad</TITLE>
            <BODY>In a medium saucepan, boil milk and sugar. Cool completely, but do not refrigerate.
            Dissolve each package of flavored gelatin separately in 1 1/2 cups of boiling water. Set aside.
            Dissolve unflavored gelatin in 1/2 cup of warm water. Add with sour cream to cooled milk and sugar mixture. Set aside.
            Spread gelatin of one color on the bottom of a 9x13 inch pan. Chill in refrigerator until set. Then put 1 1/3 cup of the sour cream mixture on the chilled, firm layer of gelatin. Keep alternating these until all gelatin is used. Be sure to chill after each addition of gelatin.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        salad
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Marinated Salad</TITLE>
            <BODY>Mix together the peas, corn, green beans, pimentos, celery, bell pepper and onion.
            In a saucepan over medium heat, combine the sugar, black pepper, salt, oil and vinegar. Bring to a boil and pour over salad; mix well to coat. Refrigerate for 24 hours.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        cake
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dessert
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Cherry Cream Cheese Cake</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat oven to 325 degrees F (165 degrees C).
            Cream the cream cheese, butter or margarine, sugar, and vanilla together until smooth. Beat in eggs one at a time. Sift together 2 1/4 cup flour, baking powder, and salt; fold into cream cheese mixture. Dredge cherries in 1/4 cup flour, and fold into batter.
            Sprinkle pecans over the bottom of an ungreased 10 inch angel food tube pan. Bottom should be completely covered. Add a few more pecans if necessary. Spoon batter into pan on top of nuts.
            Bake for about 75 minutes, or until an inserted wooden pick comes out clean. Allow cake to cool in pan. Run knife around outside edge and center tube. Ease cake out of pan, and onto plate.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Thai-Style Chicken Wings</TITLE>
            <BODY>Preheat oven to 400 degrees F (200 degrees C).
            In a large bowl combine the broth, sugar, fish sauce, vinegar, cornstarch and paprika. Set aside.
            In a hot wok or skillet add the oil, garlic and chiles. Stir fry over high heat until the garlic turns slightly golden, about 4 minutes. Add the broth mixture and stir until it boils and is reduced to about 1 1/4 cups, about 10 to 15 minutes. Keep warm.
            Place the chicken wings in a 10x15 inch baking dish and bake, uncovered, in the preheated oven for 60 to 70 minutes (until browned and crisp). Turn occasionally. Drain off the fat. With a slotted spoon, transfer the wings to a platter and pour the garlic sauce mixture over them, mixing well. Garnish with red bell pepper strips if desired.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        salad
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        breakfast
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Cranberry Salad</TITLE>
            <BODY>Combine chopped cranberries and sugar in a large, nonreactive bowl. Toss well. Cover and refrigerate for 3 hours.
            After 3 hours, stir apples, marshmallows, and pecans into cranberries. Combine yogurt and whipped topping; fold into cranberry salad. Serve immediately.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        past
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Lasagna Helper</TITLE>
            <BODY>Cook and stir the ground beef in a large skillet over medium heat until the meat is browned, about 10 minutes; drain excess grease. Pour in the water, bring to a boil, and stir in the bouillon cubes until the cubes are dissolved. Mix in broken lasagna noodles, tomato soup, onion, garlic, Italian seasoning, and black pepper. Reduce heat to a simmer, and cook until the lasagna noodle pieces are tender, about 10 minutes.
            Remove about 1 cup of sauce from the skillet, and mix with the cornstarch; return mixture to skillet, and simmer to thicken, about 3 minutes. Season to taste with salt.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        pasta
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Zesty Italian Sausage Pasta</TITLE>
            <BODY>Prepare sausage according to directions. Cool slightly; cut into 1/4-in. slices. Prepare pasta according to package directions.
            In a large saucepan, saute the onion and garlic in olive oil until tender. Stir in tomatoes and chicken broth. Bring to a simmer. Add the broccoli and cooked pasta. Cook until broccoli is tender, about 5 minutes. Add sausage; toss to combine.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        salad
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        breakfast
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Fig and Arugula Salad</TITLE>
            <BODY>Toss arugula, figs, Parmesan cheese, and pine nuts together in a large bowl.
            Drizzle honey and balsamic vinegar over salad before serving.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        pasta
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Fresh Spinach and Sun-Dried Tomato Lasagna</TITLE>
            <BODY>Cook lasagna in boiling salted water in a large pot until al dente. Drain.
            Meanwhile, heat one half tablespoon of olive oil in a Dutch oven over medium heat. Add the chopped onion, celery, and carrots, stir and cook until onions have softened. Add mushrooms and garlic and continue to cook until the mushrooms have released their liquid, 2 or 3 minutes. Add wine and cook until most of the liquid has evaporated. Stir in chopped tomatoes(include liquid), sun-dried tomatoes, and thyme. Bring to a simmer, then reduce heat to low and simmer until thick. Season with salt and pepper.
            To make the white sauce, heat remaining oil in a heavy pan over low heat. Add flour, whisk constantly until the flour begins to turn a light brown. Remove pan from heat and whisk in cream. Season with nutmeg and a pinch of salt. Remove from heat and set aside.
            To assemble, spread 1/2 cup of the mushroom sauce in the bottom of a casserole dish, add one layer of noodles, then another 1/2 cup of mushroom sauce. Arrange a single layer of the fresh spinach leaves over the sauce and drizzle them with 1/3 cup of the white sauce. Sprinkle 2 tablespoons of the grated Parmesan cheese over the spinach and top with another layer of the noodles. Repeat 5 times.
            In a preheated 375 degree F (190 degrees C) oven bake for 40 minutes. Let stand for 10 to 15 minutes. Serve warm.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        soup
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Brown Jug Soup</TITLE>
            <BODY>In a large soup pot, dissolve chicken bouillon cubes in 6 cups of water.
            Add all the vegetables, fresh and frozen, to the pot. Simmer for 30 minutes.
            Stir in cream of chicken soup. Add cheese, and mix until melted. Serve.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        pasta
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Chicken and Spinach Ravioli</TITLE>
            <BODY>In a bowl, mix the eggs, water, 2 cups flour, and salt. Gradually mix in the remaining flour until smooth. Divide dough into 2 parts. Cover, and set aside in the refrigerator 20 minutes.
            In a skillet over medium heat, cook the ground chicken until evenly brown; drain.
            In a food processor, mix the chicken, spinach, and onion. Transfer to a bowl, and mix with butter, 3 tablespoons Asiago cheese, salt, garlic powder, nutmeg, and pepper.
            On a lightly floured surface, roll out each part of the dough to 1/8 inch thickness. Cut into 2 inch squares. Place about 1 teaspoon of the chicken mixture in the center of 1/2 the squares, and top with remaining squares. Seal the edges of the squares with a moistened fork to form the ravioli.
            Bring a large pot of lightly salted water to a boil, and cook the ravioli in small batches for about 8 minutes, or until al dente. Drain, and rinse under cold water.
            Place the marinara sauce in a saucepan, and cook until heated through. Serve ravioli topped with marinara sauce and remaining Asiago cheese.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        meat
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        dinner
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Herbed and Spiced Roasted Beef Tenderloin</TITLE>
            <BODY>In a food processor, combine rosemary, thyme, bay leaves, garlic, shallot, orange zest, salt, pepper, nutmeg, and cloves. Run machine while adding oil; process until smooth. Spread mixture evenly over all sides of tenderloins. Place beef in a large glass baking dish. Cover with foil, and refrigerate for at least 6 hours.
            Preheat oven to 400 degrees F (200 degrees C). Place tenderloins on a rack in a large roasting pan.
            Roast beef in preheated oven until meat thermometer registers 140 degrees when inserted into center of beef, about 35 minutes. Remove from oven, and cover loosely with foil; let stand for 10 minutes. Slice beef, and serve.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
    <RECIPE>
        <TYPE>
        salad
        </TYPE>
        <COURSE>
        breakfast
        </COURSE>
        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Nell's Cabbage Salad</TITLE>
            <BODY>In a large bowl, combine the cabbage, green onions, noodles and almonds.
            Prepare the dressing by whisking together the oil, sugar, vinegar and seasoning packets. Pour over cabbage mixture and mix well to coat. Refrigerate until chilled and serve.</BODY>
        </TEXT>
    </RECIPE>
</RECIPES>